[Music]
we are very glad today to launch the
findings of the mixed survey the mixed
survey is a very powerful tool not only
to address the privations of children by
the government of Georgia but also to
formulate relevant policies for children
[Music]
Raul indicator Oologah no clothes should
I give Italian leash no Anya similar
with the diffuse nebulae and politicus
shame sharpies 12 solicit his level
Sagwa data tarik unit owners a
representative monitors the data the bow
and go Mario B's a severe cannot ladies
Chanchala with arteries inner guru
savage Domus caramel - with impressed
luxuries share the deliciousness of
Robespierre Avis the boxer wishes are
[Music]
transom um explosion walnuts look at the
other worker control is Sentinel
scramisaur lettuce which is the employer
sheet went on it Marlborough da matta or
e component twice component anomalies
are Shetty's classical mix it asserts
al-askari stress component rumbles the
order for the control center Montana for
Sarah 6th at tandem UNICEF converted God
zalien rear boolean for Marcia movie
[Music]
UNICEF welcomes all the findings in the
report thanks all the partners with whom
we have worked on this report and
encourages the government of Georgia to
use very actively and effectively these
findings for the well-being and to
fulfill the rights of all children in
Georgia
[Music]